Edward Dorn Papers
© 2005 University of Connecticut
Edward Dorn Papers.
undated, 1956-1993.
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center.
Dorn, Edward.
28 linear feet.
Edward Dorn was born 2 April 1929 in Villa Grove, Illinois. He studied with Charles Olson at Black Mountain College and graduated in 1955. He taught at Idaho State University at Pocatello (1961-65), the University of Essex, Great Britain (1965-1970), Northeastern Illinois University at Chicago (1970-1971), Kent State University, Ohio (1973-74) and the University of Colorado (1977-1999). Mr. Dorn died in December 1999 at the age of 70.
MSS19900049
Biography
Edward Dorn was born 2 April 1929 in Villa Grove, Illinois. He studied with Charles Olson at Black Mountain College and graduated in 1955. He taught at Idaho State University at Pocatello (1961-65), the University of Essex, Great Britain (1965-1970), Northeastern Illinois University at Chicago (1970-1971), Kent State University, Ohio (1973-74) and the University of Colorado (1977-1999).
Edward Dorn has written and published extensively. His works include: What I See in the Maximus Poems (1960), The Newly Fallen (1961), Hands Up! (1964), Geography (1965), The Shoshoneans: The People of the Basin Plateau (1966), The North Atlantic Turbine (1967), Gunslinger Book I (1968), Gunslinger Book II (1969), Twenty-four Love Songs (1969), Tree Between Two Walls (1969), Songs Set Two: A Short Count (1970), The Cycle (1971), Some Business Recently Transacted in the White World (1971), Gunslinger Book III (1972), Recollections of Gran Apacheria (1974), The Collected Poems: 1956-1974 (1975), Slinger (1975), Views (1980), Yellow Lola (1981), and Abhorrences (1990).
Mr. Dorn died in December 1999 at the age of 70.
Scope and Content
Correspondence to Edward Dorn from 1956-1993 comprises over half of the collection. Occasional letters are sent to either Peter Michelson or Jennifer Dunbar Dorn, but they are related either to the Rolling Stock or to the Dorn family in general. Significant correspondents include Amiri Baraka (LeRoi Jones), Lucia Berlin, Robert Bertholf, Stan and Jane Brakhage, Gordon Brotherston, Herb Butterfield, Tom Clark, Robert Creeley, John Daley, Donald Davie, Fielding Dawson, Clayton Eshleman, Willard Fox, Allen Ginsberg, Woody Haut, Victor Hernandez Cruz, Anselm Hollo, Harry Hoogstraten, J. H. Innskeep, Ken Irby, Terry Jacobus, Joyce Johnson, Jack Kerouac, William Levy, Ellen Mann, Michael McClure, Jim McCrary, Duncan McNaughton, Peter Michelson, Ken Mikolowski, Jeffrey Miller, John Moritz, Raymond Obermayr, Simone Okamura, Charles Olson, Joel Oppenheimer, Charles Potts, Jeremy Prynne, Tom Raworth, Joe Safdie, Ed Sanders, Nicholas Sedgwick, Al Simmons, Preman Sotomayor, David Southern, Anne Waldeman, Donald Wesling, John Wieners, John Wolff, Doug Woolf, and David Young.
Extensive notes, drafts, and rewrites of Edward Dorn's poetry include Abhorrences, Book of Poems, Captain Jack's Chaps, Collected Gran Apacheria, Cosmology of Finding Your Spot, The Cycle, Geography, Gran Apacheria, Gunslinger, Hands Up!, North Atlantic Turbine, Recollections of Gran Apacheria, Songs Set Two: A Short Count, 24 Love Songs, and Yellow Lola. Similar materials exist for Edward Dorn's works of prose, including Abilene, Abilene, The Book of Daniel, Shoshoneans, Some Business Recently Transacted in the White World, Views, and What I See in the Maximus Poems. However, various published works by Edward Dorn appear to have left no drafts or revisions to examine. Personal information about Edward Dorn is found only in the correspondence or interviews—most of the published work on Edward Dorn concerns his work, not his personal life.
Edward Dorn's publications Bean News and Rolling Stock include submissions by various authors and editorial notes. Broadsides include art and published poetry, as well as announcements of book signings or poetry readings. Taped interviews and recorded poetry readings comprise the majority of the AV materials. Photographs range from family snapshots to photos for illustrations or articles. Numerous books and periodicals have been removed from the collection and can be found in Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center. Check the library catalogue (HOMER) for call numbers.
Arrangement
The collection consists of correspondence sent primarily to Edward Dorn, manuscripts and publications created by Edward Dorn, other authors' publications about Edward Dorn or his work, other authors' submissions to Edward Dorn, assorted broadsides, audio-visual materials, and photographs.
Series I: Correspondence ( undated, 1956-1993 ) is divided into Major and Minor correspondents. Correspondence found in the Major collection include five or more letters from the correspondent, or are from prominent authors in another collection. Much of the correspondence in the Major collection is undated—these letters are filed in the front of their respective folders. The Major correspondence also includes submissions of poetry and prose if accompanied by a letter from the author. Significant correspondents include Amiri Baraka (LeRoi Jones), Lucia Berlin, Robert Bertholf, Jane and Stan Brakhage, Gordon Brotherston, Herb Butterfield, Tom Clark, Robert Creeley, John Daley, Donald Davie, Fielding Dawson, Clayton Eshleman, Willard Fox, Allen Ginsberg, Woody Haut, Victor Hernandez Cruz, Anselm Hollo, Harry Hoogstraten, J. H. Innskeep, Ken Irby, Terry Jacobus, Joyce Johnson, Jack Kerouac, William Levy, Ellen Mann, Michael McClure, Jim McCrary, Duncan McNaughton, Peter Michelson, Ken Mikolowski, Jeffrey Miller, John Moritz, Raymond Obermayr, Simone Okamura, Charles Olson, Joel Oppenheimer, Charles Potts, Jeremy Prynne, Tom Raworth, Joe Safdie, Ed Sanders, Nicholas Sedgwick, Al Simmons, Preman Sotomayor, David Southern, Anne Waldeman, Donald Wesling, John Wieners, John Wolff, Doug Woolf, and David Young.
Minor correspondence begins with unidentified correspondents' undated letters. Known correspondents with undated letters follow. The remaining correspondence is filed alphabetically for each year with unidentified correspondents who sent dated correspondence at the end of each year.
Series II: Dorn Manuscripts (undated, 1961-1993) are arranged alphabetically by title. Large manuscripts or photographs throughout the collection are filed in the oversize boxes—boxes 28 and 29. Edward Dorn's notebooks and calendars are arranged chronologically, with undated notebooks first.
Series III: Dorn Publications (undated, 1972-1991) contains Dorn's work with Bean News and Rolling Stock and includes drafts, manuscripts, revisions, artwork, etc. grouped by issue.
Series IV: Publications About Dorn (undated, 1982) includes other authors' work about Edward Dorn or his work include interviews, articles, chapters, essays, and poetry.
Series V: Submitted Manuscripts (undated) contains submitted manuscripts without cover letters are arranged alphabetically, by author, with unidentified authors filed first.
Series VI: Broadsides (undated) filed separately for preservation purposes. An accompanying separation sheet with an item indicates items associated with a specific correspondent.
Series VII: AV Materials and Artifacts (undated) filed separately for preservation purposes. An accompanying separation sheet with an item indicates items associated with a specific correspondent.
Series VIII: Photographs (undated) filed separately for preservation purposes. An accompanying separation sheet with an item indicates items associated with a specific correspondent. Dates for photographs can only be inferred from the dates of the associated correspondence and is so noted on the separation form and not in the finding aid.
Related Material
Archives & Special Collections has a substantial collection of literary materials and the papers of individuals associated with Black Mountain College. Ed Dorn materials can also be found in the following collections, also held in the Dodd Research Center: the Papers of Fielding Dawson, Charles Olson, Joel Oppenheimer, Tom Raworth, Michael Rumaker, and Ed Sanders, and in the New American Poetry Circuit Records. For detailed information on these collections please contact the curator or ask at the reference desk.
Separated Material
The following materials have been separated from the collection and cataloged:
Accordian to St. Luke. Dodd Call No.
Unser Englische Reise Albino, Albion. Berkeley: Poltroon Novelty Co., 1975. Annotated by E. D. Dodd Call No. WPS 3472
Vort. Dodd Call No. Number 1. Alpert, Barry. 1972. Dodd Peridocials.
Am Here Books. Catalogue Six, Section On. Dodd Call No.
Report from More's Creek. Ardinger, Rick. Story, Wyoming: Dooryard Press, 1986. Dodd Call No. WPS 3468
“Man is the Metaphor” Paintings by Philip Behymer Behymer, Philip. 1981-1983. 1983. Dodd Call No. XA I.10 no.32
Man is the Metaphor. Behymer, Philip. 1983. Dodd Call No. XA I.10 no.32
Am Here Books: In the Beginning was the Word. Burroughs, William, Tom Clark, et. al., contributors. Catalogue Five, 1981/82. #13 of 500. Dodd Call No.
Letters to Allen Ginsberg 1953-1957. Burroughs, William. New York City: Full Court Press, 1982. Inscribed by A. G. Dodd Call No. B2793
Under the Fortune Palms. Clark, Tom. Isla Vista, California: Turkey Press, 1982. Inscribed by T. C. Dodd Call No. C3509
Mayan Letters by Charles Olson. Creeley, Robert, ed. The Divers Press, 1953. Inscribed. Dodd Call No.
Aunty Dot and the Christmas Tree. Dawson, Fielding, New York City: The Shortstop Press, 1979. Inscribed by F. D. Dodd Call No. XA I.2 no.134
Field Dawson on Duberman's Black Mountain & B. H. Friedmasn's Biography of Jackson Pollock. Dawson, Fielding, Ontario: The Coach House Press, 1973. Inscribed by F. D. Dodd Call No. WPS 709
Penny Lane. Dawson, Fielding, Santa Barbara: Black Sparrow Press, 1977. Inscribed by F. D. Dodd Call No. A3005
The Diplomat. Dawson, Fielding, New York City: The Shortstop Press, 1977. Dodd Call No. WPS 1137
The Diplomat. Dawson, Fielding, New York City: The Shortstop Press, 1977. Inscribed by F. D. Dodd Call No. WPS 1137
Two Penny Lane. Dawson, Fielding, Santa Barbara: Black Sparrow Press, 1977. Inscribed by F. D. Dodd Call No. A3006
On the Danger of Writers Teaching. Dawson, Fielding. New York City: The Shortstop Press, 1976. Inscribed by F. D. Dodd Call No. WLB 1
The Second Diplomat. Dawson, Fielding. London: The Ferry Press, 1977. Inscribed by F. D. Dodd Call No. WPS 1138
Spirit Photography. Dick, A. P. Daytona Beach, CA: Zephrus Image, 1973. Dodd Call No. WPS 3471
9 Poems. Dorn, Edward. Niagra Frontier Review, 1965. Dodd Call No. XA I.8 no.140
Abhorrences. Dorn, Edward. Santa Rosa: Black Sparrow Press, 1990. Dodd Call No. C5426
From Gloucester Out. Dorn, Edward. Matrix Press, 1964. Inscribed by E. D., B. H., and T. R. Dodd Call No. WPS 3481
From Gloucester Out. Dorn, Edward. Matrix Press, 1964. Inscribed by E. D. Dodd Call No. WPS 338
Gunslinger 1 & 2. Dorn, Edward. London: Fulcrum Press, 1970. Inscribed by E. D. Dodd Call No. B5494
Gunslinger Book I. Dorn, Edward. Los Angeles: Black Sparrow Press, 1968. Inscribed by E. D. Dodd Call No. C5419
Gunslinger Book I. Dorn, Edward. Los Angeles: Black Sparrow Press, 1968. Inscribed by E. D. Dodd Call No. C5420
Gunslinger Book II. Dorn, Edward. Los Angeles: Black Sparrow Press, 1969. Inscribed by E. D. Author's copy. Dodd Call No. C5449
Gunslinger Book II. Dorn, Edward. Los Angeles: Black Sparrow Press, 1969. Inscribed by E. D. #20 of 250. Dodd Call No. C5450
Gunslinger Book III The Winterbook: Prologue to the Great Book IIII Kornerstone. Dorn, Edward. West Newbury, Massachusetts: Frontier Press, 1972. Annotated. (Kept with Edward Dorn Papers)Dodd Call No. D1102
Hands Up! New York City: Totem Press, 1969. Dorn, Edward. Annotated. Dodd Call No. WPS 112
Hands Up! New York City: Totem Press, 1969. Dorn, Edward. Annotated by E. D. Dodd Call No. WPS 3480
Hello, La Jolla. Dorn, Edward. Berkeley: Wingbow Press, 1978. Inscribed by E. D. Dodd Call No. C5416
Recollections of Gran Apacheria. Dorn, Edward. Turtle Island, 1974. Inscribed by E. D. Dodd Call No. WPS 3457
Slinger. Dorn, Edward. Berkeley: Wingbow Press, 1975. Inscribed by E. D. Dodd Call No. B 5496
Some Business Recently Transacted in the White World. Dorn, Edward. West Newbury, Massachusetts: Frontier Press, 1971. Inscribed by E. D. Dodd Call No. A 1530
Songs Set Two: A Short Count. Dorn, Edward. Frontier Press, 1970. Annotated by E. D. Dodd Call No. WPS 330
Songs Set Two: A Short Count. Dorn, Edward. Frontier Press, 1970. Inscribed by E. D. Dodd Call No. WPS 3478
The Collected Poems 1956-74. Dorn, Edward. Bolinas: Four Seasons Foundation, 1975. Inscribed by E. D. Dodd Call No. C 3018
The Cycle. Dorn, Edward. West Newbury, Massachusetts: Frontier Press, 1972. Annotated. (Kept with Edward Dorn Papers)
The Newly Fallen. Dorn, Edward. New York City: Totem Press, 1961. Annotated. Dodd Call No. WPS 25
The Newly Fallen. Dorn, Edward. New York City: Totem Press, 1961. Annotated by E. D. Dodd Call No.WPS 3479
The North Atlantic Turbine. Dorn, Edward. London: Fulcum Press, 1967. Inscribed. Dodd Call No. B 5495
Twenty-four Love Songs. Dorn, Edward. Frontier Press, 1969. Annotated by E. D. Dodd Call No. C 1054
Yellow Lola. Dorn, Edward. Santa Barbara: Cadmus Edition, 1981. Dodd Call No. A 4378
Little Lists. Gildzen, Alex. Twin Lakes: Toucan Press, 1973. Dodd Call No. WPS 3470
Poems All Over the Place, Mostly `Seventies. Ginsberg, Allen. Cherry Valley, New York: Cherry Valley Editions, 1978. Inscribed. Dodd Call No. WPS 1283
The White Room. Harwood, Lee. London: Fulcrum Press, 1968. Inscribed by L. H. Limited edition number - presentation 13/15. Dodd Call No. C 1902
To Max Douglas. Irby, Ken. Tansy 4 / Peg Leg Press, 1971. Inscribed. Dodd Call No. WPS 738
A Set. Irby, Kenneth. Lawrence, Kansas: Tansy Press, 1983. Inscribed by K. I. Dodd Call No. X II.5 no.3
Orexis. Irby, Kenneth. Barrytown, New York: Station Hill Press, 1981. Inscribed by K. I. Dodd Call No. XA II.1 no.54
Smart But Not Wise. Kahn, Lloyd. Bolinas: Shelter Publications, 1972. Dodd Call No. XA I.8 no.139
Dog Stories. Kaszubowski, Kevin, ed. 1993. Dodd Call No. A 4368
The Uses of Error. Kermode, Frank. 1986. Dodd Call No. WBS 1
On the Mass Bombing of Iraq and Kuwait, Commonly Known As “the Gulf War” with Leonard's Shorter Catechism. Leonard, Tom. Stirling, Scotland: AK Press, 1991. Dodd Call No. WDS 3
Legacy from Haniel Long. Long, Anton, compiler. Naples, New York: The Brookside Press, 1977. Inscribed by A. L. Dodd Call No. WPS 3473
Wolf Eyes. McClure, Joanna. San Francisco: Bearthm Press, 1974. Inscribed by J. M. Dodd Call No. WPS 764
Little Odes, Poems & a Play, The Raptors. McClure, Michael. Los Angeles: Black Sparrow Press, 1969. Dodd Call No. C 717
Love Lion Book. McClure, Michael. San Francisco: Four Seasons Foundation, 1966. Dodd Call No. C 186
Poisoned Wheat. McClure, Michael. San Francisco: 1965. Inscribed. Dodd Call No. WPS 890
Solstice Blossom. McClure, Michael. Arif Press, 1973. Inscribed by M. M. Dodd Call No. XA I.1 no.222
The Book of Joanna. McClure, Michael. Berkeley: Sand Dollar, 1973. Dodd Call No.
Address Unknown. McCrary, Jim. San Francisco: Road Kill Press, 1990. Inscribed by J. M. #3 of 10. Dodd Call No. WPS 3465
Edible Pets. McCrary, Jim. 1985. Dodd Call No. WPS 3466
Abra. Meltzer, David and John Brandi. Hipparchia, 1976. Dodd Call No. XA I.8 no.74
French Broom. Meltzer, David. Oyez, 1973. Inscribed. Dodd Call No. WPS 1907
Six. Meltzer, David. Santa Barbara: Black Sparrow Press, 1976. Inscribed. Dodd Call No. C 3047
The Eyes, the Blood. Meltzer, David. San Francisco: Cranium Press, 1973. Dodd Call No. WPS 549
13 Sounds. Morris, James Ryan. Pinecliffe, Colorado: The Poetry Subway, 1977. Inscribed by J. M. Dodd Call No. XA I.3 no.82
He Has Heard. Morris, James Ryan. Denver: The Croupier Press, 1970. Inscribed by J. M. Dodd Call No. WPS 3467
Passing From the Provinces: Three Fragments. Morrow, Bradford. Santa Barbara: Cadmus Editions, 1981. Dodd Call No. WPS 3464
Morning Glories. Naoya, Shiga. Allen Say and David Meltzer, translators. Oyez, 1975. Inscribed. 1981 Cambridge Poetry Festival Programme. Dodd Call No. WPL 13
In Cold Hell, In Thicket. Olson, Charles. 1953. Inscribed. Dodd Call No.
Letter for Melville 1951. Olson, Charles. Black Mountain College, 1951. Inscribed. Dodd Call No.
Maximus, From Dogtown - I. Olson, Charles. San Francisco: The Auerhahn Press, 1961. Inscribed by C. O. Dodd Call No. C 5428
One World Poetry P79. San Francisco Blues, 1958. Dodd Call No. WPS 2135
Clean Asshole Poems & Smiling Vegetable Songs. Orlovsky, Peter. San Francisco: City Lights Books, 1978. Inscribed by P. O. Dodd Call No. A 3009
So Much Plotted Freedom. Out to Lunch. London: Reality Studios, 1987. Dodd Call No. XA I.9 no.98
Tree Between Two Walls. Pacheco, Jose Emilio. Translated by Edward Dorn and Gordon Dodd Call No. XA I.1 no.208
Brotherston. Los Angeles: Black Sparrow Press, 1969. Inscribed by E. D., G. B., and E. P. #148 of 250.
Serious Iron. Parker, Linda, ed. 1971. Dodd Call No.
A Night Square Candlemas 1971. Prynne, J. H. Inscribed. Dodd Call No. XA I.1 no.221
A Night Square Candlemas 1971. Prynne, J. H. 1973. Inscribed by J. P. Dodd Call No.
Day Light Songs. Prynne, J. H. 1968. Annotated by E. D. Dodd Call No. WPR 169
Down Where Changed. Prynne, J. H. London: The Ferry Press, 1979. Inscribed by J. P. Dodd Call No. WPR 504
Fire Lizard. Prynne, J. H. Barnet: Blacksuede Boot Press, 1970. Dodd Call No. WPR 366
Into the Day. Prynne, J. H. Saffron Walden: Saffron Press Ltd., 1972. Inscribed by J. P. Dodd Call No. WPR 722
Kitchen Poems. Prynne, J. H. London: Cape Goliard Press, 1968. Inscribed by J. P. Dodd Call No. WPR 726
Marzipan. Prynne, J. H. Cambridge: Peter Riley, 1985. Dodd Call No. WPR 567
News of Warring Clans. Prynne, J. H. London: Trigram Press, 1977. Inscribed by J. P. Dodd Call No. WPR 686
The Oval Window. Prynne, J. H. Saffron Walden: Saffron Press Ltd., 1983. Dodd Call No. WPR 499
The White Stones. Prynne, J. H. Lincoln: Grosseteste Press, 1969. Inscribed by J. P. #103 of 477. Dodd Call No. C 1756
Wound Response. Prynne, J. H. Cambridge: Street Editions, 1974. Inscribed by J. P. Dodd Call No. XA I.4 no.56
Queen Elizabeth I, San Francisco: Bellerophon Books, 1972. Annotated by E. D. Dodd Call No. XA I.9 no.97
6 Poems. Raworth, Tom. Milwaukee: Woodland Pattern, 1985. Inscribed by T. R. Dodd Call No.WPR 720
A Serial Biography. Raworth, Tom. Santa Barbara: Water Table Press, 1977. Inscribed by T. R. Dodd Call No. A 4369
Ace. Raworth, Tom. 1974. Inscribed by T. R. Dodd Call No. WPR 708
Ace. Raworth, Tom. Goliard Press, 1974. Inscribed by T. R. and E. D. Dodd Call No.WPR 457
Act. Raworth, Tom. London: Trigham Press, 1973. Inscribed by T. R. Dodd Call No. B 5493
Bolivia: Another End of Ace. Raworth, Tom. London: Secret Books, 1974. Inscribed. Dodd Call No. WPR 709
British Horse Tortured! Cambridge: 1986. Raworth, Tom. Inscribed by T. R. Dodd Call No.
Cloister. Raworth, Tom. Northampton: Sand Project Press, 1975. Inscribed. Dodd Call No. WPR 710
Common Sense. Raworth, Tom. 1976. Inscribed by T. R. Dodd Call No. WPR 718
Four Door Guide. Raworth, Tom. Beacon Press, 1979. Inscribed by T. R. Dodd Call No. WPR 383
From Eternal Sections. Raworth, Tom. Dublin: hardPressed Poetry, 1990. Inscribed by T. R. Dodd Call No. WPR 717
Heavy Light. Raworth, Tom. Inscribed by T. R. Dodd Call No. WPS 2191
Lazy Left Hand. Raworth, Tom. Actual Size, 1986. Inscribed by T. R. Dodd Call No. WPR 711
Lèvere de Poche. Raworth, Tom. Durham, North Carolina: Regulator Press, 1984. Inscribed by T. R. Dodd Call No. WPS 2065
Lion Lion. Raworth, Tom. London: Trigham Press Limited, 1970. Inscribed by T. R. Dodd Call No.WPR 727
Moving. Raworth, Tom. London: Cape Goliard Press, 1971. Inscribed by T. R. Dodd Call No. C 3885
Nicht Wahr, Rosie? Berkeley: Poltroon Press, 1979. Raworth, Tom. Inscribed by T. R. Dodd Call No. WPR 719
Selections From His Forthcoming Book Writing. Raworth, Tom. Durham, North Carolina: Regulator Press, 1977. Dodd Call No. WPR 716
Six Sonnets for Gothenburg and Geneva. Raworth, Tom. Cambridge: Infolio Productions, 1987. Inscribed by T. R. Dodd Call No. WPR 212
Sky Tails. Raworth, Tom. London: Lobby Press, 1978. Annotated by T. R. Dodd Call No. WPR 713
That More Simple Natural Time Tone Distortion. Raworth, Tom. 1975. Inscribed by T. R. Dodd Call No. XA I.2 no.58
The Big Green Day. Raworth, Tom. London: Trigram Press Limited, 1968. Inscribed by T. R. Dodd Call No. C 5425
The Mask. Raworth, Tom. Berkeley: Poltroon Modern Poets Volume One, 1976. Inscribed. Dodd Call No. XA I.7 no.17
The Relation Ship. Raworth, Tom. Goliard Press, 1966. Inscribed by T. R. Dodd Call No. C 5415
The Thoughts of Captain Alexis. Raworth, Tom. Cambridge: Infolio and Scorribanda Productions, 1987 Dodd Call No. WPR 715
Tracking. Raworth, Tom. Bowling Green, Ohio: Doones Press, 1972. Inscribed. Dodd Call No. C 2081
Tractor Parts. Raworth, Tom. Spectacular Diseases, 1984. Inscribed by T. R. Dodd Call No. WPR 724
Writing. Raworth, Tom. Berkeley: The Figures, 1982. Inscribed by T. R. Dodd Call No. XA II.1 no.69
Chameleon's Cadmium. Rodney, Janet. 1976. #6 of 250. Dodd Call No. WPR 723
Vail of Tears. Schindling, Eric. Unidentified Poets Coop., 1977. Inscribed by E. S. Dodd Call No. WPS 3462
The Wishing Bone Cycle. Slowstream, Jacob. Norman, Howard Allan, translator. San Francisco: Zephyrus Image. Dodd Call No. WPM 1
From: ALASHKA. Tarn, Nathaniel and Janet Rodney. London: Permanent Press, 1977. Inscribed by N. T. and J. R. Dodd Call No. WPR 463
The House of Leaves. Tarn, Nathaniel. Santa Barbara: Black Sparrow Press, 1976. Inscribed by N. T. Dodd Call No. C 5447
Willow. Tarn, Nathaniel. Inscribed. Dodd Call No.
The Book of Daniel Drew. Introduction by Edward Dorn. New York City: Frontier Press, 1969. Inscribed by E. D. Dodd Call No. WPR 728
The Caian. Cambridge: Gonville and Caius College, 1979. Dodd Call No.
Ox Herding A Reworking of the Zen Text. Weishaus, Joel and Arthur Okamura. San Francisco: Cranium Press, 1971. Dodd Call No.
Memoirs of an Interglacial Age. Whalen, Philip. The Auerhahn Press, 1960. Inscribed. Dodd Call No. C 5427
Ace of Pentacles. Wieners, John. New York: James F. Carr & Robert A. Wilson, 1964. Inscribed by J. W. Dodd Call No. C 5448
Chinoiserie. Wieners, John. San Francisco: Dave Haselwood, 1965. Inscribed by J. W. Dodd Call No.WPS 3474
Nerves. Wieners, John. London: Cape Goliard Press, 1970. Inscribed. Dodd Call No. C 5418
Pressed Wafer. Wieners, John. Buffalo: The Gallery Upstairs Press, 1967. Inscribed by J. W. Dodd Call No.WPS 32
Selected Poems. Wieners, John. Bungay: The Chaucer Press, 1972. Inscribed by J. W. Dodd Call No.C 5417
Woman. Wieners, John. The Institute of Further Studies, 1972. Inscribed. Dodd Call No.
Periodicals:
The American Book Review. New York City: The American Book Review, 1980. Volume II, Number 4, May-June 1980. Dodd Call No.
The American Poetry Review. Volume 21, Number 5, September/October 1992. Dodd Call No.
The Arts at Black Mountain College 1933-1957. New York City, The Edith C. Blum Art Institute. Dodd Call No.
Bingo. New York City: Bingo, 1980. Dodd Call No.
Boulder County Business Report. Volume 7, Issue 8, August 1988. Dodd Call No.
Boulder Monthly. Volume I, Number V, March 1979. Dodd Call No.
Bradford Morrow Bookseller Ltd., Catalogue 9. Annotated. Dodd Call No.
Sagetrieb Bunting, Basil and George Oppen, eds. Orono: University of Maine at Orono, 1982. Volume 1, Number 1, Spring 1982. Dodd Call No.
Chicago Review. Volume 39, Number 1, 1993. Dodd Call No.
The Daily Kent Stater. “ Creative Arts Festival.” April 11, 1973. Dodd Call No.
PO&SIE. Deguy, Michel, ed. Paris, Librairie Classique Eugene Belin, 1977. Number 3. Dodd Call No.
Dental Floss West Branch, Iowa: The Toothpaste Press, 1978. Volume I Number III. Dodd Call No.
:that:. Dignazio, Stephen and Stephen Ellis, eds. May 1992. Dodd Call No.